Help on method_descriptor in file:

file.seek = seek(...)
    seek(offset[, whence]) -> None.  Move to new file position.
    
    Argument offset is a byte count.  Optional argument whence defaults to
    0 (offset from start of file, offset should be >= 0); other values are 1
    (move relative to current position, positive or negative), and 2 (move
    relative to end of file, usually negative, although many platforms allow
    seeking beyond the end of a file).  If the file is opened in text mode,
    only offsets returned by tell() are legal.  Use of other offsets causes
    undefined behavior.
    Note that not all file objects are seekable.

